NO ANIMALS WERE HARMED DURING THE
FILMING OF THIS PRODUCTION
Göktuğ!
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
Brother!
Osman!
Charge!
Alps!
Brothers!
My Bey.
-I will make all of them...
-May you hold on!
My Bey, pull it off.
Göktuğ, my brother, hold on!
Kill them all!
May you hold on.
My brother.
I bear witness that there is no god but
Allah...
Göktuğ!
Göktuğ.
Alps!
Göktuğ is still alive. Take him away!
Come on now!
My brother.
Savcı!
Do you even hear yourself, brother?
Nikola is a guest in this Tent.
Don't you remember what they did to us
while we were guests in Kulacahisar?
Savcı!
If we do the same thing, we'd be no
different from them!
We aren't that kind of profiteers who act
like friends while trying to stab others.
Are we, brother?
Dündar Bey, take Savcı and come with me.
Don't you know what kind of a trouble
is getting close to us?
Don't worry.
I will be there with him.
Gündüz Bey...
... after everything, you actually look
like a good person.
I'm sorry for what I did to you.
Or rather, for the things I did with
Flatyos.
Patience.
Gündüz Bey!
Enough already.
I also started to lose my patience,
Nikola.
Arslan Bey, wait a second.
Speaking of Flatyos...
... where is he?
He's no longer a commander of mine.
He is set out on his on now.
Where are you, Osman?
The battle has only just started brothers!
To the victory!
Charge!
Don't you ever retreat!
This is an order!
Charge!
Do you understand me now, uncle?
I feel the same, my nephew.
I also want to take the head of that
Nikola dog.
However, we need to be patient.
We are here for a reason.
As long as we don't attract the anger of
Geyhatu, everything will be okay.
Osman is not here, uncle.
What will we talk about?
Let Osman attract the anger of Geyhatun on
himself.
And together, we will take back
Kulacahisar.
We need to be patient.
I'm starting to lose my patience, uncle!
I have to look at Nikola's face while I
don't know what Osman is up to.
I have my own limits.
Real Arslan is not who is impatient but
who's capable of controlling his anger.
We need to be patient for Kayı.
We shall go back to Tent now.
As you say, uncle.
We will be patient for Kayı.
Oh, praise be upon my Valiant!
Where did you come from?
I came from Karabağ to help Kara Osman
defeat our enemies, my Bey.
How wonderful! Praise be upon all
Valiants of Karabağ!
Come on now!
Helen!
Bala!
Go after Helen!
I had done my duty and then I came here.
But Osman did not.
He deceived us all.
It means he doesn't recognize might of
Geyhatu.
Thus, you need to talk Geyhatu about your
troubles on your own.
Don't worry Yalvak Arslan. I will tell
Geyhatu that you tried at least.
Tell Geyhatu that if he comes with his
army, I will also stand against him!
All Kayıs listen to my words but Osman
acts on his own.
Geyhatu is free to attack Osman.
However, he can't touch even a single
hair of other Kayıs.
If he does, I will fight him too.
I like courage.
You are too courageous, Yalvak Arslan.
Understand this well, Nikola.
Us Turks aren't so serious when our enemy
is as small as you but...
... we will combine all paths when the
enemy is as big as Mongols.
Your paths combine with Cerkutay, Yalvak
Arslan.
What do you mean, Nikola?
Do you know where Cerkutay is, Yalvak
Arslan?
At the hands of Osman.
That's right.
Ayaz!
Yes, my Bey!
Go to Yalvak's Tent at once!
Tell my uncle and brother not to try
hard for peace!
As you order, my Bey!
My Osman, it feels like we missed taking
castles after all.
Someday we will take Inegol and Bursa
too, my Bamsı Bey!
Let's go!
Let's go, my child!
Targun Hatun!
My father is caged down, Osman Bey. I just
couldn't wait!
Help him at once!
Alps!
Follow Targun Hatun!
Helen!
Come at me! You unlucky Hatun.
Everything started when you and your
father came!
Die!
You will share the same end with Sofia!
Bala!
Damn it!
Be quick!
My Bey, the castle is finally with his
owner.
Oh, praise be!
Kulacahisar is a home to Turks from
now on!
My Brothers! Rip out every flag you see
at the castle!
As your order, my Bey!
Let's go brothers.
Kara Osman is finally approaching.
Damn it! Who is this dull stick?
Who are you?
Your death, Flatyos!
Do you really want this, you dull stick?
You are so brave, Flatyos.
I like it.
-Targun Hatun.
-Osman Bey!
He is not my father!
They took my father away!
Targun Hatun, don't worry.
I'm going to bring your father.
Bala!
As I said, I'm going to bring your father
to you!
We couldn't capture Helen.
She ran away.
Let's go.
Aren't you a tough dull stick?
You are dead now.
It's nice of you to bear death with a
smile.
Kulacahisar is not yours anymore.
I'm laughing as to this.
What are you saying?
You hurt me!
I bear witness that there is no god
but Allah...
... and I bear witness that Muhammad
is the servant and Messenger of Allah.
- Brother.
- My Bey.
- Are you okay?
- We took the castle.
So, I'm okay, my Bey.
They seared my wounds.
Mashallah, my brother!
Let's go.
- Bamsı Bey.
- My Osman!
Mashallah, my valiant!
What's up with you?
Nothing. I'm fine.
Son of Ertuğrul Gazi, Osman Bey!
Don’t kneel!
Keep standing!
Stand like the mountains
against the evil!
As your Alps, we're with you
until we die!
As long as you progress
in the path of battle…
… clearing those roads is
our sacred duty!
- Allahu Akbar!
Looks like Osman isn’t coming.
Everyone completed their duties.
It’s time to dismiss this meeting.
Next time, I’ll be waiting
for you at Kulacahisar.
We can also continue
with where we left off.
Uncle. You should come too!
Uncle-nephew statue.
Now I will--
Nikola!
I’ll kill you!
Soldiers, don’t interrupt!
- Step aside!
- I will kill you!
- Savcı!
- Savcı Bey!
- Stop!
As soon as we get out of this
mess, I’ll do the same to them!
Let me go!
Ensheathe the swords!
Savcı! Stop!
You’re barbaric.
My Bey!
What is it, Sertaç?
My Bey, a Greek is here.
He escaped from Kulacahisar.
- So?
- Osman Bey!
What happened to Osman Bey?
Osman Bey conquered Kulacahisar!
- Long live, Osman Bey!
My Alps! My brothers!
My valiants!
This is not an honour,
a victory day.
This is the day we
tear apart the acts of evil!
Our greatest shame comes from not the
enemies who took this castle with tricks…
… but from those who are
from our own kind, own blood!
They took advantage of
Ertuğrul Gazi’s illness and…
… worked together with the
enemies both outside and among us!
From now on, our children
won’t feel this kind of shame!
We won’t allow it!
From now on, we tear
apart the chains on our feet!
Our next target is İnegöl Fortress!
We shall not stop until
we capture the infidels’ castle!
- We shall not stop!
Let those who are
from our own blood…
… get tricked by the enemy!
Now, those who sharpen their
swords with faith will be victorious!
- Allahu akbar!
Osman brought the end
of all of you with this victory!
You’ll be crushed by
the Greek and Mongol armies!
Beys! I lost a castle,
you lost everything you have left!
Checkmate!
Dündar Bey, Gündüz Bey. Come.
No one goes to Kulacahisar.
No one helps Osman.
Save yourselves first.
We should return to the Tent, uncle.
And put an end
to these useless negotiations.
Osman did his move.
Not it’s my turn.
Don’t make moves out of anger.
The enemy’s castle is conquered.
And the conqueror is our brother.
Your brother risked the whole
Tent’s future by conquering that castle.
We need precautions, Gündüz!
Geyhatu will come
again and shed blood!
What are you talking about, uncle?
We should let him kill Osman
and be done with it?
What about you, Savcı?
Is that what we should do?
Brother. If you’re not doing
well, you should stay here with Bamsı Bey.
I’m okay, my Bey. Don’t worry.
Once I’m on my horse, the rest is easy.
Very well.
Let’s go, brother.
Bamsı Bey!
The castle is yours now.
Don’t worry, son! While we’re
here, no one will dare come here!
If they do, they’ll meet their maker.
Watch out for yourself.
When the day comes,
we’ll establish our state side by side!
Inshallah, my Osman.
Don’t worry!
Bamsı is here as long
as Allah lets him!
- Thank you!
- My valiant!
Here.
If you allow me, I’d like
to come with you, my Bey.
You’re very welcome, Gence Bey. Come.
We’re done with this castle.
Let’s go to our Tent.
Peace is impossible now.
They are all over each other.
We should save ourselves.
Osman must not take
Cerkutay to Geyhatu.
Let’s set off at once.
I’ll end Osman myself.
Osman and Bala are nowhere
to be seen. Aygül also left.
Targun Hatun also left running.
They’re up to something.
Osman must have gone to Kulacahisar again.
He’s obsessed about that castle.
Bamsı Bey and his
Alps aren’t here either.
If you’re right, and he takes the castle…
If Ertuğrul Bey wakes up
and hears about it…
Then Osman will be
the successor and everything will be over.
Once Dündar and Savcı Bey are
here, we’ll see what their intentions are.
If they still don’t want to
make a move to defeat Osman…
… we’ll tell them that
there is no time left.
If Osman Bey is trying
to take Kulacahisar, a war will break out.
We’re in a war already.
I’m talking about the war
in Kayı Tent, Davud brother.
They are brothers.
Sure they are.
The worst kind of war.
You don’t know who
your enemy and friends are.
Look at me! You’re
trying to do your own thing again!
Of course, you’re
relaxed, Davud brother.
Once a war breaks out,
no one will care about a potter!
Everyone will be
interested in your swords.
You’re exaggerating again.
My only intention is to trade,
brother. I’m trying to make ends meet.
But unfortunately, no one
will make ends meet in Kayı Tent.
[Call to Prayer]
My Bey! Is there any good news?
There is, Master Davud!
Welcome, Osman Bey!
Thank you, Ahmet Alp!
Gence Bey! This is our
Ahmet Alp. He protects the Tent.
I’m Gence Bey.
My Bey! This arrival
looks like a blessed one!
With the permission of Allah,
and veterans’ efforts…
Kulacahisar is conquered once again.
Mashallah!
Kulacahisar is conquered!
- Allahu akbar!
Kulacahisar is conquered.
Everything will be more difficult now.
Master Davud, our guest is
tired from battle. Take care of him.
With all my heart, my Bey!
I’m honoured, my valiant.
I’m also honoured.
Before we conquered it,
this Kulacahisar Castle...
... was all about soulless rocks,
empty rooms.
After it was washed with martyrs' blood
and blessed by the names of our creator...
... then it became home,
and faith.
Children! The enemy will come!
They will test your faith!
They'll try to take your homeland!
they'll try to rape your honour!
What will you do then?
We'll fight!
- Will you give them this castle?
- Never!
- Will you give them your flag?
"I'd rather die" you say. Is that correct?
- It is not!
It is not!
Dead or alive, this castle
will not be lost again!
Doesn't matter if they're Greek or Mongol.
We'll crush them all!
But they will not take this castle!
Children! They will not say Bamsı and
his Alps died defending the castle!
"Bamsı and his Alps didn't surrender
the castle" they will say!
- Allahu Akbar!
Children! Kayı is becoming a beylic!
It's dreaming of becoming a state!
Children! Don't burry this
dream with yourself! Live that dream!
Children! Be an old veteran like
Bamsı Beyrek!
Be glorious, be victorious!
Children! Until the enemy surrenders,
until the people of Kayı sleep in peace...
You don't get the sweet
release of death!
- Allahu Akbar!
My Osman. My dark-eyed Osman
who conquered Kulacahisar again!
Osman. The fact that you conquered
the castle again makes your aunt proud.
But remember. Other things you want to do
for the second time doesn't make me happy.
Aunt. You're their elders.
Give them advice.
You did it again, Osman.
You threw the Tent into the fire.
You don't care about the situation your
uncle, your brothers are in, do you?
Do you, Osman Bey?
My Bey!
Osman Bey is here.
The people and Alps
are celebrating, my Bey!
My Osman will be here any second.
He'll stand by the door. When he
sees that his father's eyes are open...
Father!
- Father!
- Son!
Father!
Are you okay?
My veteran father!
My brave father!
I see that you're doing well.
You'e doing well.
Where were you, my Osman?
What news did you bring?
I kept my promise, father.
Kulucahisar is again yours.
It is in your land.
My Allah, thank you.
Thank you so much.
I saw you, my son.
I saw you.
I saw our lands.
I saw the horizon.
I saw the future.
Tell me about the future, Osman.
Tell me about the future.
The war is coming, my father.
This war will continue until we destroy
the ones...
who want to end Kayıs forever.
I am not going to stop until I kill them.
After that, my people will relieve.
Mosques, madrasahs...
I will build arsenals.
I will build so that our state takes root
in this land.
So that our knowledge grows with our
faith.
So that our sons and daughters spread
it through the world.
Then...
I give my blessings to you.
My father.
Alhamdulillah.
(praise be to Allah)
My father.
My one and only father.
Osman is acting like a Bey.
I hope it ends well.
They say some were born to be Bey...
and some always try to act like a Bey.
It's high time we had a talk, Targun.
How does it feel to lose a castle
two times, Helen?
Feels like being captured two times
by the same man.
Vladius and Helen.
Two great soldiers!
We lost Kulucahisar.
Don't you think it was so fast, Helen?
Osman's men infiltrated into us.
They opened the gates!
And the Kulucahisar fell, right?
And you run like a rat instead
of fighting like a soldier, right?
And Vladius.
You were supposed to kill Osman,
weren't you Vladius?
While sitting in Yavlak Arslan's dirty
tent, everybody was waiting for Osman...
I was thinking that "oh you can wait
for hours, but Osman is dead."
But meanwhile, he conquered
Kulucahisar.
Osman didn't come, Nicola.
A yahoo showed up instead of him.
I killed him.
A yahoo?
A yahoo.
I didn't want you to kill a yahoo, Vladius.
I wanted you to kill the lion.
If you listened to me and killed Osman
when we had the chance...
now I wouldn't be hearing these insults,
and you wouldn't lose Kulucahisar.
I send you to Sogut to fix
your fault, Vladius. But you failed.
Moreover, Osman captured Cerkutay
because of your foolishness!
Can you imagine what will happen if
he takes Cerkutay to Geyhatu?
I will kill him.
I'll kill Osman.
I would be very happy, Vladius.
But I am down for even Cerkutay.
I'll take you Helen.
As you know, we can't go to Kulucahisar.
Right?
Can you at least find Osman, Vladius?
We need to foresee every move
of Nicola.
He won't simply attack the castle.
He will make an unexpected move.
As to Yavlakarslan, he must have heard
that we have Cerkutay.
He is going to come like a fly goes
around the dirt.
He is going to come here himself.
Then I'll kill him.
My Bey, he can't dare to come to
our tribe.
He is not going to come to our tribe,
Göktuğ. He'll cross our path.
Be ready. I will destroy whoever
disobeys Kayıs.
First of all, I want it to be good.
It is actual that Beys marry more than
one Hatun.
Our Osman Bey made this decision to
keep the family name alive.
What I am supposed to do as
Osman Bey's first Hatun is...
to tell you about him.
To prevent any flaws that can happen
to this man who is the hope for Kayıs.
What a noble way of thinking.
I am willing to listen to you.
He doesn't like talking about wars and
favours he made.
He is thoughtful in his tent.
He thinks of the future of Kayı.
You need to be silent those times.
Then he says "my Bala."
I mean...
He's going to call you Targun,
of course.
"How was your day, tell me."
he says.
He listens to you with a clean smile
on his face.
He listens, then he passes out again.
Don't be offended.
My Sheik father was also like that.
Big man are thoughtful.
Bala Hatun, this must be hard for you.
- Don't contunie.
- I have to say this.
Our Osman Bey...
Osman...
likes his beard warm.
Cook it fast, or just heat it.
- In the afternoon.
- Bala Hatun.
- In the afternoon...
- Don't torture yourself.
Osman Bey and I...
We are actually...
You, Targun Hatun.
You are going to give him sons and
daughters.
This is why I am okay with this marriage.
I know, I know.
Thank Lord.
We took the castle back.
My horse is waiting for the race.
You didn't forget, right?
I remember.
Are you not willing to do it?
Gonca Hatun, why are you staring?
Men like racing, right?
We do, but what's the point?
Osman Bey compares Bala to others.
- My Bey does the right thing.
- Is that so?
Gonca Hatun.
We are going to race, right?
Race yourself.
Gonca Hatun!
From now on, our job is diffucult,
my Bala.
But, you will have hard days ahead of you.
Don't ever let them to break your heart.
You shall be strong.
Don't buckle under anyone!
Now they are going to try to attack
you over Targun Hatun.
Defend both yourself and Targun Hatun.
You told me to follow her. You suspected
her, now you want me to defend her.
Yes, my Bala.
That's what I want for now.
You wanted me to marry.
I accepted.
Now I want you to defend the Hatun
I will marry. Please accept this.
Why did you choose her?
Not someone else but her?
My Bala, I told you to follow her.
I told you that I suspected her.
I was right.
Targun Hatun works for Nicola.
What?
What are you talking about, my Osman?
She admitted it.
She did it to save his captive
father from Nicola.
What I want is to make Nicola believe
that his game is still on.
I want to trick him, my Bala.
That's why I marry her.
- Is this the reason?
- Of course.
Then I don't agree you marrying her.
- Even if it's a part of your game...
- Can I come in?
Come, aunt.
Don't tell anyone for now.
Come.
- Son.
- Speak, aunt.
Ayaz Alp.
He has been martyred.
Ayaz.
Inna Lillahi wa inna ilayhi raji'un.
("Verily we belong to Allah, and
verily to Him do we return.")
I will make them pay!
I will take revenge from whoever did this!
The man who you are going to take
revenge from left this note on Ayaz Alp.
Lion hunter Vladius.
Vladius!
You killed my brother!
Ignoble dog!
I'll kill you!
Aunt, give us a minute.
My heart is burning, brother.
Tell me what you have to say.
My condolences, brother.
I heard about the Kulucahisar.
May your conquer be blessed.
What can I say, Osman?
You made Geyhatu our enemy.
You put Kayıs in a difficult
situation.
They will arrive here anytime.
After that move, we seperated forever.
Your path is selfishness.
My path is about the future of this tribe.
Our paths have never crossed anyways,
brother.
Don't be afraid of Geyhatu.
I'll handle it.
Ah, Osman, ah.
Oh my brother.
How can you handle?
How?
Don't worry brother.
I know what to do .
Let me visit my martyr now.
Brother.
My Ayaz.
So you wanted to leave early.
Is that right, my Ayaz?
Did you want to leave early?
You wanted to arrive at our Lord's
heaven.
You deserved it brother.
You deserved it.
Thank to Allah.
Thank to our Lord.
I have brothers who know the
meaning of martyr.
And they console themselves with...
shadada.
A big, strong and faithul brother he was.
Tell his story to kids of Kayı.
My Ayaz.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
(in the name of Allah, the merciful and compassionate.)
Targun Hatun works for Nicola.
She did it to save his father who
was captured by Nicola.
What I want is that Nicola keeps
believing that his game is still on.
I will trick them, my Bala.
This is why I marry her.
Bala.
- Are you fine, my beautiful daughter?
- I'm fine mother.
Why would I be not fine?
You are lost in thoughts all alone.
I was thinking about what a
great guy Osman Bey is.
Of course, he is.
He is, but...
Aren't you offended at all, Bala?
For now, no one should know.
Aren't you sad at all?
Why should we talk about that, Gonca?
Everything happens as it's destined.
Today, we conquered Kulucahisar. We fought
together just like the old days.
Right, Aygül?
How did we strike at the heathens?
We did indeed. Now our swords are
freed from their sheathes.
Osman Bey won't stop the holy war.
It would be so sweet now if we hadn't
received bad news from Ayaz Alp.
Then we'll pray for our martyr,
and make his soul proud.
-Bring Osman's Qur-an.
-Yes, Selcan Mother.
He said that he will take Kulucahisar
and he did.
If he says that he'll take İnegöl
and do it...
...who can do anything? After now,
telling him that he can't don't matter.
Our laws allow us to select a Bey
before Ertuğrul Bey recovers.
In this time of conflict, the election
of the Bey must be done.
Without a Bey, Osman won't listen to
anyone.
Are we sure that the beys in the
tents won't support Osman?
We'll tell them about the situation and
show them the dangers we are facing.
-Osman won't listen to this decision, uncle.
-Then we'll try every way, including exile.
If needed, we will shed blood for
the future of the tents.
I said if needed. If needed, my nephew.
-What about Bamsı Bey?
-We should convince him before it gets to that.
You'll do that.
Tomorrow, we should start talking to
the beys.
You are right, uncle.
We should.
Inegöl Castle.
Wow, wow, wow. İnal Bey.
It's a great honor to see you here, İnal Bey.
Now you must be thinking. ''What did I do
to sit here instead of eating with the rats.''
For a captive, rats or mouses make
no difference.
Whoever accompanies you, the food
is still a poison.
These Turks never change.
-I guess you don't like captivity.
-If you had the same blood...
...you would kill yourself after all
those defeats.
I already died, İnal Bey.
But I've reborn again.
Do you know why, huh?
To banish your kind, the Turks
from these lands.
You'll die a lot, Nikola.
I won't die this time.
Do you know who'll die?
Osman.
And who will kill Osman?
Who will? Who?
Helen. I think we should send a word
to Targun Hatun. We should say...
...if she doesn't kill Osman,
Lord Nikola...
...will use your father's bones...
...to make a necklace.
A necklace.
You can't do this!
They will kill my daughter!
Your daughter isn't so alive while you
are in my hands anyway, İnal Bey.
-Take him away.
-Let me go.
As he deserves.
A room with the rats.
Helen. While Targun Hatun kills Osman,
you'll kill Bamsı Bey who defends him.
You are sending me to death, Nikola?
Don't go to death, Helen.
Send Bamsı instead.
I don't like excuses.
Thank you, wife.
What are you thinking? It's been
a while since I saw that expression.
What expression?
The expression of 'I know what to
do to you'.
Tomorrow, I'll talk to the beys.
Before my brother dies, the next bey
should be elected.
Before your brother dies?
Yes. While Osman struggles with Nikola,
we'll gather the council.
Savcı will seek it and it's possible that
he'll win.
-So?
-So, Osman won't have it.
-They'll draw swords...
-Then?
One dies, the other becomes a
brother-slayer.
-Only Gündüz and I will be left.
-Then? Then?
Then, it's apparent.
I'll be the Bey of the Kayı.
Finally. Finally!
Finally, Dündar Bey!
Be like that all the time.
Be like that so that I can support
you with all my heart and power.
Now, you gave me
a real purpose.
You woke me up from dead sleep.
My brother Osman wants the
best for the Kayı.
He thinks that the best is the destruction
of all enemies.
He struggles for that.
Allah knows that he is doing well.
He saved me from captivity twice.
He reconquered Kulucahisar.
He saved Söğüt.
We are in his debt.
What are you saying, Savcı?
But he doesn't know that the enemy
grows and the Kayı can't get on with that.
For the future of the Kayı,
he must be stopped.
How will that happen?
For this to be taken care of lawfully,
the council should gather before...
...my father Ertuğrul Ghazi passes away.
And I should be elected.
Gündüz?
I'm not sure about him.
He is too fond of my brother Osman.
What about Dündar Bey.
He will support me.
He is the one that you shouldn't
be sure about.
What do you mean, wife?
Have you heard something.
Even if Dündar Bey wants to give up,
Hazal Hatun won't.
We might be on the same side because of
Osman. But without him, we'll be enemies.
You should know that.
My Allah, Kulucahisar Castle is
reconquered with your bless.
And it is a property of Islam, again.
O' Allah, without your bless, we wouldn't
be honored with Islam, or the holy war.
We bow our heads to your blessing.
Don't make us think that it is us
who wins the victory.
Protect us from conceit, arrogance, greed.
O' Allah, don't let us be like
the heathen.
Make our brother Azad a neighbor
to the companions of our prophet...
...for being a martyr in the holy war.
-Amin.
-O' Allah, these Ghazis who opened their hands...
...ask for the same fate.
-Amin.
Hear our prayers, my Allah.
Tomorrow is the day of holy war.
You'll come with me.
And the alps that are left here...
...will do their last duty for our
martyr brother.
-As you command, my bey.
Gence Bey, come with us tomorrow.
-My path is your path, Osman Bey.
-Thank you.
Yavlak Arslan's men don't know you.
You should scout the way.
And tell us if there is a trap.
Will I draw my sword and join
the holy war then, Osman Bey?
That's up to you.
Come, come. Bring it, my girl.
Bring it.
Just like that, show it to
Targun Hatun.
Targun, you'll be the wife of
a Kayı bey.
Your aunt Hazal will have a pretty
dress sewed for you.
You can take off your steppe clothing
and wear those in the tents.
Thank you but I'm not used to
wearing such fancy things.
No way. You are a new bride.
You should be fancy.
Thank you.
It's very pretty.
Selcan Hatun, are you empty-handed?
Giving a gift to the new bride
is of our customs.
Have you forgotten it?
The best gift is an advice, my girl.
That's all I can give you.
Is stinginess called advice now,
Selcan Hatun?
Look, my girl, a fire can burn down
the tents.
And fire can cook food.
Your fire should bring light to your
husband and the tents.
Be like a drop of water.
But don't forget...
...a drop of water stinks when it touches
hot iron, and becomes a poison in a viper's mouth.
Be the mother of pearl so that it can
be a pearl in your mouth.
Be like soil, my girl. But don't forget.
Both thorn and herb grow on soil.
For this reason, be like a flower,
my girl.
Enjoy your meal.
What a great honor, Geyhatu!
You gave me a seat after my request.
You wanted a place to sit.
I told you to go...
...and sit at Kulucahisar.
Osman took that castle from you.
Now, you need a seat
to sit. Sit.
Not sitting was better, it seems.
Stop grumbling. Sit.
-Speak.
-Osman stepped over your order, Geyhatu.
While I was expecting peace in
Yavlak Arslan's tent, he took Kulucahisar.
The castle that you gave me.
So, Osman took your castle.
Can't Yavlak Arslan control Osman?
No, only you can control
Osman?
What if I kill all of you and
give everything to Osman...
...make him the Bey of Beys?
Tell me why this
would be wrong.
Speak. I want to know you.
I'll be honored. You made
Yavlak Arslan your margrave.
But his real purpose is to destroy you
and build a Turkish state in Anatolia.
But don't be afraid.
He can't do such a thing.
If you ask what I want,
I want to banish all the Turks.
Mongols can stay.
-Why?
-Because you aren't Muslim.
Neither Rome nor I have a problem
with you.
What about Osman?
If you make Osman the Bey of Beys,
and if he gets the pledge of all Turks...
...then, Geyhatu, neither Rome
nor the Mongols can stand.
Osman scared you.
Osman should scare you, too, Geyhatu.
It should so that you can solve the problem.
I like advices.
Tie him in where he sits.
What is this now?
What is this?
What kind of diplomacy is this?
Is this steppe diplomacy.
-Take him away.
-Barbarian.
This is how you should sit
at İnegöl.
So that Osman can't take your seat.
Little lord is gone.
What should we do with that Osman?
Möngke? Möngke?
Should we behead Osman?
Or should we boil him
with his brothers?
Mongke? Möngke?
Möngke isn't here.
Möngke is dead.
Osman Bey! Osman Bey!
Osman Bey!
You are making a great mistake,
Osman Bey.
-What is that mistake?
-Yavlak Arslan.
You shouldn't incur Yavlak Arslan.
It will be a shame.
You deserve a better death.
Our lives are in the hands
of Allah.
We'll die as he wants.
I wish to die standing.
Thank you, Cerkutay.
Thank you.
If I have to kill you, I'll
remember what you've just said.
You grovel...
I'll kill you standing.
- You're not a Muslim, right?
- Yes.
Will you be a Muslim
when you marry Osman Bey?
She'll become a
Muslim first, then she'll marry him.
Yes.
Excuse me, Hatuns.
Let's see what you're up to.
Oh.
Sit, daughter.
My Bala.
My beautiful daughter.
My darling.
Well done.
You showed everyone how Sheikh Edebalı's
daughter should be.
Always be like that.
Why don't you say yourself?
I've learned so much from you.
Yes you have.
However, you have.
Look at Hazal.
I've done many things but...
Hazal is still the same.
- Bala!
- What happened?
Targun Hatun left the tent.
Aygül followed her.
Go follow her..
Look after her.
Let's not disappoint Osman.
My Bey, there are
Yavlak Arslan's guards ahead.
Thanks, brother.
Yavlak Arslan set a trap.
I know what to do.
They're coming.
Come, Osman.
Get ready. Wait until they come.
If they fight, they will fight
in a wounded body.
Get ready. Wait for my sign.
Wait.
- They are our watchmen.
- Damn it!
Yavlak Arslan!
Now we'll talk in your way of
understanding.
Brothers, tie them to our horses.
- Come on!
- Make them wear your clothes.
You'll give an account for
your traps, your treasons...
and your harms.
My Bey.
This endless war harms us.
No one asks how people is.
Söğüt is also the same.
The people can't do anything for
fear of Nikola's attack.
We need peace.
However...
it's not possible because of Osman Bey.
Now we're in trouble because of Geyhatu.
We'll die starving if we can't sell goods.
Do you want a solution from us?
If you can't find a solution, how
can we find any?
Consult our Bey, Ertuğrul Ghazi.
We wouldn't be like
that if Ertuğrul Bey was healthy.
Anyone who holds a seal is the ruler.
When he has the seal, what can we do?
Savcı Bey is right.
We need to elect a new Bey...
to make things better and
prevent Osman from preventing it.
May Allah make it late.
It'll be a mistake to do that before my
father dies.
Osman will refuse that.
It's the right thing to do.
Choose your side, Gündüz Bey.
You're the only one left.
You still don't understand, do you?
Then let me say.
I side with Ertuğrul Ghazi.
I don't want to hear about Beys
as long as he is alive.
Savcı...
you still fight with Osman.
However, you should know that.
I won't be like you.
I'm with my father.
When the time comes... I'll be
with...
whoever he wants.
If you excuse me, uncle.
At least...
He chose his side.
Choose your sides, brothers.
Do you want an infinite war or...
a tent which grows and gets
rich day by day?
Osman Bey and Bamsı Bey
won't forgive that.
I'll talk to Bamsı Bey.
He loves me, he'll listen.
He has to.
You can't kill me, Osman. You're
not that dumb.
If you kill me, all the Turk Beys...
will become your enemy, not just Beyhatu.
Don't worry.
Think about what you'll say.
Tie them all.
Kumral Abdal.
Osman Bey.
Look at this boy. I have
hope from him.
Easy, Kumral Abdal.
Don't worry. The rest is ours.
Your mystery is solved.
Bungler.
- What is Yavlak Arslan doing there?
- So, Möngke and Cerkutay's partner...
is Yavlak.
He got into deep water.
What will we do now?
Yavlak will win.
Osman will lose.
Geyhatu and Çobanoğulları will fight.
Let's save Yavlak.
Then let's kill Osman.
I knew you were a traitor.
Targun!
Come here!
I saw you swallowed the paper.
You can't run away.
Traitor dog!
You lied to Osman Bey.
It's none of your business...
Osman Bey has a beautiful hatun.
You always saw me as an enemy.
However, just our paths were different.
I was going to kill Geyhatu.
So, I was going to end the
Mongol oppression.
I underestimated you.
So that you were going to
end the oppression...
What were you doing with Möngke?
Möngke is an idiot.
Osman, it's still not too late...
for a powerful Turk
state in Anatolia.
What are you saying?
Geyhatu should die today.
Or it'll be too late for all of us.
My Bey!
Are you fine, my Bey?
Flatyos.
What, Osman?
Can't you hold a sword?
Don't worry.
I'll take care of you.
Don't forget that I've saved you, Yavlak.
Let's kill Osman now.
You know, when you hurt a lion...
you should kill it.
I'm grateful to you and Nikola.
What are you up to again, Targun?
Put your sword down.
- I didn't do anything wrong.
- Osman Bey told us some things.
However, I see there's something else.
Targun!
Do you want to save your father or
cause trouble?
- Traitor!
- Stop, Aygül.
Who was he?
What was written on that paper?
What paper?
If everyone knows, it's
not a secret, Bala.
What secret is she talking about?
Whatever. Let's talk in the tent.
Come on.
Come on!
I said you'll see Azrael.
No one can take our lives...
that Allah gives..
to us.
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com